kerchoonz.com 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy » Free Legal Music Downloads or Streams - Register Free at Kerchoonz

> **Privacy Policy for www.kerchoonz.com**
> 
> This Privacy Policy ("Policy") supplements the Terms of Use, any other terms and conditions which we may require you to adhere to (collectively referred to as the "Terms"), and forms part of those Terms and should be read in conjunction with them. You can view them here [insert link to Terms of Use]. 
> 
> Expressions used in the Terms have the same meaning in this Policy. 
> 
> Any reference to " **we** ", " **us** " and " **our** " in this Policy is to Ganghut Limited care of Henderson Loggie Sinclair Wood & Co, Gordon Chambers, 90 Mitchell Street, Glasgow, G1 3NQ 
> 
> Any reference to " **you** " or " **your** " in this Policy, means you as a user of the www.kerchoonz.com the " **Website** "). 
> 
> **We are committed to protecting your privacy.**
> 
> This Policy explains how your personal information (meaning any information about you which is personally identifiable like your name, address, telephone number or email address, generally referred to throughout this Policy as "personal information") will be used.
> 
> For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, we are acting as a data controller, and you shall be the data subject. Our data controller registration number is Z1505584. 
> 
> Please note that this Policy only applies to the collection of your personal information by us directly on this Website and the use of that personal information by us and by those whom we authorise. 
> 
> This Policy does not cover the use of any of your personal information which you may divulge on third party websites which are linked from this Website, and you should carefully read any other privacy policy on those third party websites.. 
> 
> By accessing and continuing to use the website, you accept the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with any part of our Policy then you should not use the Website or register any account with the Website. 
> 
> We may update and amend this Policy from time to time and any changes will be posted on the Website and it is your responsibility to revisit this Policy from time to time to view any amendments / updates. 
> 
> This Policy was last updated and was effective on 8th August 2011. 
> 
> **The information we collect from you.**
> 
> We may require you from time to time to register an account to use various services on the Website and / or update your current registration details (including payment details) - and in such instances we collect and store your personal information which you provide us with during the registration process.
> 
> As an example we collect: name, age, email address, PayPal account, photos etc, postcode.
> 
> We also collect information (as is common with most websites) from “cookies” or other such similar devices which store and sometimes track information about your use of the Website (see section entitled "Do we use Cookies" below), and irrespective of whether you register an account with us.
> 
> We may also collect personal information when you disclose any such personal information to us or otherwise through your general use of the Website (for example when you make a posting, comment, a complaint or enquiry or provide feedback to us; or when you submit an entry to a competition or prize draw; or when you request to be sent communications by us, such as updates or newsletters; in monitoring your communications sent via and use of the website to ensure and check compliance with our Terms)
> 
> **How do we use the information which we collect from you ?**
> 
> We use information we collect from you, to help us improve your experience of using the Website.
> 
> We may use your personal information to:
> 
>   1. monitor, develop and improve the Website and so improve your experience; and / or
>   2. assist us in administering the website services or any payments due to or from you; and / or
>   3. process and deal with any complaints or enquiries which we receive which are made by, or about, you and your issue of the Website; and / or 
>   4. investigate any suspected breach of any of the Terms; and / or 
>   5. to monitor your compliance with the Terms, and thereby allow us to check postings or submissions on the Website, forum messages ; and/or 
>   6. to administer any competition prizes which you may be entitled to, including the right to publish or otherwise make available a list of prize winners and/or 
>   7. notify you of any changes to the Website (including by email to you), including any postings or comments made by other users on your profile - you may opt out of such emails using your account settings page, but we reserve the right to send you important Kerchoonz information. 
> 

> 
> We shall only send you updates regarding the services on the Website (by email, telephone and SMS) and information concerning third party products when expressly requested to do so by you. After requesting such information, we shall provide you with opportunities to cancel such requests, and for the avoidance of doubt, you can cancel such information requests any at time by emailing us to privacy@kerchoonz.com and stating that you do not wish to receive any such further communications from us. 
> 
> Please note that certain aspects of the personal information you supply will be available on your public profile page for other users to view. Your name, username, profile picture thumbnail will be available in the Kerchoonz search results, and those limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so that your friends or other users can find your profile page easily and send you a friend request. As a registered user, you will have the option of setting your Kerchoonz profile to private so that it can only be viewed by your friends in the Kerchoonz network. Other users will also be able to see any posts or comments you make on the website. 
> 
> We may pass on non-personally identifiable information about you (e.g. ip address) to third parties, for purposes such as aggregating how many people in the website like a certain artist, or to help personalise advertisements and promotion to suit your demographic. We believe that this will benefit your experience of the Kerchoonz website. 
> 
> We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to other internet sources such as blogs, chartrooms, newspapers etc to supplement your profile. Where such information is sued, we generally allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connections of this information to your profile. 
> 
> We use your IP address (in a non-personally identifiable format) to analyse the statistical use of the website so we can help improve the website experience for users and understand more about our users. 
> 
> **Internet Awareness **
> 
> Please note that some of your profile information will be public to other users of the website. You should not therefore divulge any information which you consider 'private' Please exercise discretion and care when posting any information on the website. 
> 
> **How can you amend your personal information ? **
> 
> When you register your personal details on the Website to register an account or for certain other services (e.g. such as our weekly newsletter) you may subsequently change or update your personal details (including you user name and password) at any time via your account log-in. You should ensure that you update your details as soon as possible with any relevant changes. 
> 
> **Do we use "Cookies" ?**
> 
> A cookie is a small amount of data sent from our server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 
> 
> Cookies and other such similar devices allow us to compile anonymous, aggregated statistics of the usage of the Website by users (i.e. you), so that we can understand how users (i.e. you) use our Website. This includes allowing us to understand such things as how popular certain web pages or advertisements are. 
> 
> Cookies allow us to improve the structure of our Website, and please note that we cannot identify you personally by using Cookies, as all data collected by the Cookies is anonymous apart from our referral cookie for the Kerchoonz Kwidget - this cookie is required to identify you so that we may pay you for your referrals (please see Terms of Use) and cannot be removed. Cookies and other such similar devices can also assist and facilitate your use of the Website by: 
> 
>   1. allowing you to carry information across pages of our Website and thereby avoiding having to re-enter information; 
>   2. allowing you to access stored information within your registration area; 
>   3. allowing us to tailor content and / or advertisements to match your preferred interests or to hopefully assist in avoiding us showing you the same adverts repeatedly. 
> 

> 
> **How can I remove Cookies ?**
> 
> It is common for most internet browsers (e.g. Firefox or Windows Explorer) to be automatically set up to accept Cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse a cookie or ask your browser to show you where a cookie has been set up. 
> 
> However please note that certain services on the Website are only activated by the presence of a Cookie and therefore if you choose to refuse cookies, particular features of this Website may not be available to you. The Kerchoonz Kwidget cookie may not be removed. 
> 
> If you wish to remove Cookies by disabling them, please click on the 'Manage Cookies' section of the Interactive Advertising Bureau website http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ 
> 
> **Do we share your information with third parties ?**
> 
> We may pass your information to other parties for the following reasons: 
> 
>   1. solely where relevant, your user name and information you voluntarily provide in your profile (e.g. profile or user name) and which you have which you have registered with us, will be published on areas of the Website such as the forums, chat rooms or pages where user submissions are displayed and this will be the identity by which you are known on those areas. Other users of the Website will therefore be able to identify you and contact you by your user name or profile) 
>   2. we will pass your personal information on to our employees, contractors, suppliers and/or agents so that we are able to administer the Services provided to you by us now or in the future; 
>   3. we may pass on some general statistical information about the website user base, sales patterns, traffic volumes and any such related matters to reputable third parties (including our advertising partners) who will handle such information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998, but please note that these details will not include information personally identifying you; and 
>   4. we may disclose your personal information to the police, regulatory bodies or legal advisers in connection with any alleged criminal offence or suspected breach of any of the terms of use as we may other otherwise be required by law and we will co-operate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity of or locate anyone breaching the terms of use or otherwise for the prevention or detection of crime or the apprehension or prosecution of offenders. 
> 

> 
> **Links and third party advertising**
> 
> We are not responsible for the privacy policy for any website which you click through to form our own site, and you should check that website's own privacy policy. Adverts on this website may use cookies also, and you should check the advert homepage for more information. Security and how do we protect your information? We abide by the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998, and we will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. We reserve the right to transfer your personal data outside of the EU, and in such instances we shall ensure that our partners abide by the EU-Safe Harbor Scheme. 
> 
> **Contact details**
> 
> You can email us with any questions, queries or complaints to [privacy@kerchoonz.com](mailto:privacy@kerchoonz.com)
> 
> Or you may write to us at Ganghut Limited care of Henderson Loggie Sinclair Wood & Co, Gordon Chambers, 90 Mitchell Street, Glasgow, G1 3NQ. Please mark all correspondence 'Privacy/Kerchoonz'.
